Guide to the Mick Moloney Irish-American Music and Popular Culture Field Recordings AIA.031.002
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series IV: Audio Inventories for Grammy Preservation Project, 2007-2009
  - Carroll, Liz (aiamm299, aiamm230), circa 2007-2008 (Box 81, Folder 85)
  - Baker, Duck (aiamm301b1), circa 2007-2008 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - The Green Fields of America (aiamm302b1p1, aiamm303b1p2, aiamm304b1p1, aiamm305b1p2, aiamm306b1p1, aiamm307b1p2, aiamm308b1p3), 2008 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Concert at Cherry Tree (aiamm309), 2008 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Concert in Geneva, NY (aiamm310b1p1, aiamm310b1p2), circa 2007-2008 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Carroll, Liz (aiamm311b1), Practice in Philadelphia (aiamm311b2p1), circa 2007-2008 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Practice in Philadelphia (aiamm312b2p2, aiamm312b2p3), circa 2007-2008 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - NAFFM Concert (aiamm313b1p1, aiamm313b1p2), 2008 (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Concert at the Cherry Tree (aiamm314b1p1, aiamm314b1p2), circa 2007-2008 (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - O'Donnell, Eugene and Mick Moloney (aiamm315b1p1, aiamm315b1p2), circa 2007-2008 (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Curran, Eamon (aiamm316b1), O'Donnell, Eugene (aiamm316b2), circa 2007-2008 (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - O'Donnell, Eugene (aiamm317, aiamm318, aiamm319, aiamm320b1, aiamm320b2), circa 2007-2008 (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - Casey, Bobby (aiamm321b1), 2008 (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - McComiskey, Billy, Brendan Mulvihill, Andy O'Brien (aiamm321b2, aiamm321b3), 2008 (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - Mulvihill, Martin and Ceili Bands (aiamm322b1p1, aiamm323b1p2, aiamm323b1p3, aiamm323b1p4, aiamm324b1p5), 2008 (Box 82, Folder 14)
  - O'Donnell, Eugene (aiamm325, auamm326, aiamm327), 2008 (Box 82, Folder 15)
  - Rafferty, Mike (aiamm328, aiamm329b1p1, aiamm329b1p2), 2008 (Box 82, Folder 16)
  - Lafferty, Fr. Charles Patrick (aiamm329b2), circa 2007-2008 (Box 82, Folder 17)
  - Moloney, Mick, Jimmy Keane, and Robbie O'Connell (aiamm330), circa 2007-2008 (Box 82, Folder 18)
  - Concert in Augusta, WV (aiamm331), circa 2007-2008 (Box 82, Folder 19)
  - Irish Music Concert (Moloney et al) (aiamm332), circa 2007-2008 (Box 82, Folder 20)
  - Moloney, Mick, Eugene O'Donnell, Tim Britton, and Dancers (aiamm333b1, McCullough, Larry (aiamm333b2), Hughes, Richard (aiamm333b3), The Flying Cloud (aiamm333b4), circa 2007-2008 (Box 82, Folder 21)
  - Concert in Augusta, WV (aiamm334b1p1, aiamm334b1p2, aiamm335), circa 2007-2008 (Box 82, Folder 22)
  - John Vesey Trio (aiamm336), 2008 (Box 82, Folder 23)
  - Standeven, Tom and Pupils (aiamm337b1), John Vesey Trio (aiamm337b2), circa 2007-2008 (Box 82, Folder 24)
  - John Vesey Trio (aiamm338, aiamm339b1p2, aiamm339b1p2), circa 2007-2008 (Box 82, Folder 25)
  - The Johnstons (aiamm340), 2008 (Box 82, Folder 26)
  - Harte, Frank and Mick Moloney (aiamm341), circa 2007-2008 (Box 82, Folder 27)
  - Clancy, Paddy (aiamm342b1p1, aiamm342b1p2), 2009 (Box 82, Folder 28)
  - Carroll, Liz (aiamm344b1p1, aiamm344b1p2), circa 2007-2008 (Box 82, Folder 29)
  - Brittingham, Frank (aiamm344b1p1, aiamm344b1p2), 2007 (Box 82, Folder 30)
  - Heaney, Joe (aiamm345b1p1, aiamm345b1p2), 2009 (Box 82, Folder 31)